hifixxx.com 2015-08-14

# HiFiXXX.com - Privacy Policy

At HiFiXXX.com, we respect and protect the privacy of our customers and those who use our website. The following Privacy Statement provides details about how your personal information is collected and used. This privacy statement applies to the network of HiFiXXX.com websites, products and services that are located in, but not limited to the HiFiXXX.com.In domains.  

## Information Collection and Use:

HiFiXXX.com is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. HiFiXXX.com collects information from our users at several different points on our website.  

## Sharing and Usage:

We will never share, sell, or rent your personal information with third parties for their promotional use. Occasionally, we enter into contracts with third parties so that they can assist us in servicing you (for example, providing customer service). The contracts prohibit them from using any of your personal information for their own purposes, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information we provide to them. We may also disclose information to partners who introduced you to HiFiXXX.com services in order to ensure they are properly compensated for their efforts. Lastly, we may disclose or report personal information in limited circumstances where we believe in good faith that disclosure is required under the law. For example, we may be required to disclose personal information to cooperate with regulators or law enforcement authorities, to comply with a legal process such as court order, subpoena, search warrant, or law enforcement request.  

## Links:

Some of our sites provide links to third-party websites, such as those of our business partners and online advertisers. While on these sites, HiFiXXX.com or its partners may collect information about you. Because HiFiXXX.com does not control the information policies or practices of these third parties, you should review their privacy policies to learn more about how they collect and use personally identifiable information.  

## Security:

We take every precaution to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information by using industry-recognized security safeguards such as firewalls, coupled with carefully developed security procedures to protect your information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration. When we ask for sensitive information, such as credit card numbers, we protect it through the use of encryption during transmission, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

HiFiXXX.com takes care to reinforce the importance of our website visitors' security and privacy among our employees. Our employees are trained and required to safeguard your information and, using physical, electronic and procedural safeguards, we restrict access to personal information to those employees and agents for business purposes only. Additionally, we use internal and external resources to review the adequacy of our security procedures.

## Notification of Changes:

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the HiFiXXX.com Website. So our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  
Please do not hesitate to contact us.
